Bruno Hoffmann

brunohoffmanndev@gmail.com +353 083 4891713

Professional Summary

Dedicated full stack developer with 3+ years of experience in web development using JavaScript, microservices and APIs. Appreciate writing clean code, with good practices and design patterns. Good teamwork and communication.

Skills

API Design and Development Software Development Standards Teamwork and Collaboration Technologies: Node, NestJS, Keycloak, Typescript, PHP, Laravel, Microservices

Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, MySQL

Datastreams: Kafka, RabbitMQ

Staff training Strong Interpersonal and Communication Skills

Experience

Senior Software Developer Maitha Tech Dec 2021 - Current São Paulo, Brazil

Working in an e-commerce company, participating in a context that covers the part of sending SMS, E-mail. My team also handles the authentication part using Keycloak and the new customer registration part. I have a strong focus on building new requested features and fixing bugs. The product I am working with my team is a new product, which currently has a client that is Armani. Technologies used: NestJS, Typescript, Docker, Kafka, RabbitMQ, MongoDB, Microservices, Vue.js, GitLab, Atlassian JIRA and Confluence.

Full Stack Developer Meu Crediário

July 2021 - dec 2021 Santa Catarina, Brazil

System for credit management for shopkeepers and chain stores. Development and maintenance of APIs for customer credit analysis, serving large networks. Integration with various services such as credit bureaus, credit cards, bank slip,

SMS. Development of ETL routines. Development of a wallet in NestJs.Management and teamwork with third parties for integrations and partnerships. Technologies used: NodeJS, Typescript, CQRS, PostgreSQL, NestJS, Docker, Angular, React, Vue.js, Microservices, RabbitMQ, Kubernetes, GitLab and BigQuery.

Full Stack Developer Apresenta.me

Jan 2021 - July 2021 Santa Catarina, Brazil

Acting as a fullStack programmer in a real estate CRM, creating improvements and fixing system errors. Used technologies: Laravel, PHP, MySQL, VueJS 3, Typescript, HTML, CSS, JQuery, GraphQL, Github, JIRA.

Internship Developer Área Central

July 2020 - Dec 2020 Santa Catarina, Brazil

System specialized in the business model of business associations. Used technologies: PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery, Gitlab, JIRA.

DBA Casa Automação

Nov 2019 - May 2020 Santa Catarina, Brazil

Acting in the database in the creation of tables, functions, Trigger, Views, and in the creation of project documentation and new system resources, creating tasks for the development of new resources or new projects. Starting to work as a web designer on the company's institutional website, using Laravel on the back-end and front-end using HTML5, CSS3, bootstrap and jQuery. Used technologies: Laravel, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JQuery, Gitlab, JIRA.

Education

Associates degree: Systems for internet

June 2021 - Current Santa Catarina, Brazil

Estácio

Bachelor of Science: Information system

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020 Santa Catarina, Brazil

UNIDAVI